Talking about ICICI LBARD, now this is also a stock
on which we will focus because
its results are going to come next week i.e. on Tuesday.
So Janvi, please tell me what
is expected here?  Its results will be mixed
if seen comparatively
because the premium earned
can increase by about 15%.
Their premium earnings can be seen coming around Rs 550 crore.
Now the effect of this is that
auto sales which we saw in the last quarter have been
a bit sluggish.  Due to which there
seems to be a slight difference in their income.  At the same time,
one good thing will be
for this company that it will gain its market
share in the auto segment.  So
this definitely seems to be a positive point.
If we talk about profits, then
there can be an increase of about 12%.
Due to the reduction in cost expenses, there seems to be a spread up in profits.
If we talk about APE, there
can be an increase of up to 40% in usage.
This time APE growth may come at around Rs 670 crore.
But if we talk about the combined ratio, then
a slight increase can be seen there.  The
combined ratio may increase from 102.2
to 103.4.  There will be an impact on the company's
claims and other expenses
due to increase.
But if we look at it all in all, a stable set of
numbers will be seen coming.  We are fine.  So,
stable numbers can come. In the
auto segment of ICICI LBARD, it will be
seen gaining some market share.  However, there may be some pressure in the segment.
But look at ICICI LBARD, if you
look at the futures market at this time, it is the
second biggest lender after Muthoot Finance.
Trading at the day's low.
ICICI Lar is also down and before the results,
ICICI Piden is also down by about 2.5%.
Mixed results are also expected